

Jacob Petersen

JCB.PETERSEN1995@GMAIL.COM 951-227-6991 GITHUB.COM/JCBPETERSEN1995

Profile

Motivated designer and junior web developer with experience creating websites and web applications. Strong collaboration skills and proven history of succeeding within career roles. High-line automotive industry and customer service background. Experience in HTML, CSS, Javascript, MYSQL, Express, Node.JS and more.

Experience

AUTOMOTIVE SERVICE ADVISOR, MERCEDES-BENZ; LITTLETON, CO – JUNE 2018 - MARCH 2020 AUTOMOTIVE SERVICE ADVISOR, MERCEDES-BENZ; ESCONDIDO, CA – FEBRUARY 2017- JUNE 2018

As a Service Advisor I'm responsible for promoting automotive services and repairs by identifying the need for and selling service work while maintaining a high degree of client satisfaction. I'm a representative of the Mercedes-Benz brand and implement all process and procedures in order to provide the best for our clients.

SHIFT LEADER, STARBUCKS COFFEE COMPANY; NORCO, CA - 2013-2017

As a Starbucks Shift Supervisor, I assisted the store manager in executing store operations during scheduled shifts. I deployed partners and delegate tasks to create the Starbucks Experience for our customers by providing legendary customer service with prompt service, quality beverages and products, and maintaining a clean and comfortable store environment. I was responsible for modeling and acting in accordance with Starbucks guiding principles.

Education

University of Denver, Denver, CO - Full-Stack Web Development Program - 2019 – Present Centennial High School, Corona, CA – High School Diploma - Graduation 2013

Skills

- EXCELLENT COMMUNICATION VERBALLY, OVER THE PHONE, AND THROUGH MESSAGES
- HTML/CSS
- JAVASCRIPT / JQUERY
- EXPRESS / REACT / NODE.JS
- FULL-STACK WEB DEVELOPMENT

- BOOTSTRAP / UI KIT
- API
- MYSQL
- HANDLEBARS
- MONGODB
- MONGOOSE

References

JASON CESTARO, GENERAL MANAGER - MERCEDES-BENZ OF ESCONDIDO - 310-877-4201

AMBER MARTIN, STORE MANAGER - STARBUCKS COFFEE COMPANY - 909-560-0762

JEROME SEUBERT, SERVICE MANAGER - MERCEDES-BENZ OF LITTLETON - 303-900-4768